Kankan title
It's careless banchou!
Careless Banchou!
Yes, I'm Banchou inadvertently. It's careless bancho.
Oh~. If you have that many surprise marks on your face.
Yes, that's right.
There are many careless bosses in the idol world,
But this one must be a very good one.
I think so.
I see.
I thought that inadvertently being a watchdog was a bad thing. Me too.
That's right.
Not a good person.
A good person is a good person is not a good person.
That's right. When I first started being called "careless boss,
I was like Ucuka and careless boss,
Uguka's careless boss!
I was like, "Oh, it's me, too.
But then, on Uguka's radio show,
But then, a radio show on Uguka started a corner with a program featuring Shigeo Serizawa, the careless leader of Uguka,
Have you gained that much recognition?
I am beginning to think that this is something to be thankful for.
I am starting to think that I should be thankful for this,
I'm starting to think that I should be thankful,
I've gotten used to it.
What kind of carelessness do you think you have done wrong in the past?
It's really just everyday life,
You can tell from everyday life?
I often find myself thinking, "This one, this one, this one..." For example, the other day, I was taking a bath, and I was making up,
For example, the other day, I was taking off my makeup in the bath,
For example, the other day, I was taking off my makeup in the bath, and I didn't have any makeup on that day.
But I accidentally took my turn.
Is this a girl's land?
No, I don't think so,
I showed the mirror and I didn't have any makeup on,
I was shocked and had a good time,
Is that what this is about?
I'm going to take it all off.
That would be careless.
Is there anything else?
I often have a manager tell me to pull out my credit card before leaving the hotel,
I'm often told by my manager to pull out my credit card before leaving the hotel,
It's kind of convenient.
It's a key, isn't it?
But I told them to pull it out before leaving the hotel,
But if I told them to leave without pulling it out, they would just leave without pulling it out,
But when I was like that, a member said, "Let's go downstairs,
And they helped me out.
Is that right?
Moa-chan was careless.
That's right.
Because I was nominated.
It was right after he told me,
It was awkward, wasn't it? It was also awkward to tell him.
To the manager.
So I told the members,
And they helped me.
And who is helping you?
Sora.
That's funny.
But there's a lot going on.
What else?
Can I give you one more thing in return?
Also, a careless episode.
You are the leader in carelessness, aren't you?
Also, if you are an idol, you wear a costume, don't you?
Yes, I do.
And under the costume, they wear an inner kimono,
I was wearing it, but I put it in the trash by mistake.
What?
You took it off?
I took it off and threw it in the trash when I was cleaning up,
Mr. Selison, there were about two occasions when I found innerwear in the trash.
Twice?
That's a little bit suspicious,
I'm not sure.
But I ran out of hoodies the other day. Mine.
What?
I have one of the members' hoodies,
Me?
My hoodie is gone,My hoodie is missing,
I'm not really conscious of it,
I'm not really conscious of it, but I've thrown it away so much that I think I might have given it a chance.
I see.
It is really frustrating.
Well, if it had been me, I would have done it.
No, I really feel like I can't say anything even if I was stuffed.
Yakanta Idol.
Well then,
Oh, I accidentally made a mistake.
Kettle and Idol.
I'm sorry, this is too much radish.
It's so natural. What do you call it?
What do you mean? I don't know. It's just... It's natural.
This program is...
Mr. SOTO
Keisuke
Momoa
Mr. Guruguru
This program was provided by Laure-san!
Thank you very much! By Byron!